forex-url.net 2010-06-08

# Forex Trader And Short Url -

أخر تحديث لسياسة الخصوصية لـ " [ Forex Trader And Short Url](http://www.forex-url.net/) " بتاريخ 28-08-2009

Privacy Policy for http://www.forex-url.net

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at adv@http://www.forex-url.net. 

At  http://www.forex-url.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://www.forex-url.net and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers, http://www.forex-url.net use log files. This includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, browser type, internet service provider ( ISP ), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
http://www.forex-url.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitorsâ€™ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include  [Google Adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense/), . 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on http://www.forex-url.net. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

http://www.forex-url.net has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices.  http://www.forex-url.net's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

نحن نستعين بشركات إعلانات ( طرف ثالث ) لعرض إعلاناتها على موقعنا وستعرض لك عندما تزور موقعنا ويحق لهذه الشركات ان تستخدم معلومات حول زيارتك لهذا الموقع والمواقع الويب الاخرى وكل ما ستحتاج إليه هو الاسم والعنوان او عنوان البريد الإلكتروني او رقم الهاتف, وذالك لاجل تقديم إعلانات حول البضائع والخدمات التي تهمك ,   
**مثلاً إعلانات شركة غوغل google**  
* تستخدم Google، بصفتها مورِّدًا خارجيًا، ملفات تعريف الارتباطات لعرض الإعلانات على موقعك.  
* ستتمكّن Google، باستخدام ملف تعريف الارتباط [ DART](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)، من عرض الإعلانات للمستخدمين استنادًا إلى زياراتهم لمواقعك ومواقع أخرى على الإنترنت. 

* * *

http://www.forex-url.net allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the  http://www.forex-url.net site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the  http://www.forex-url.net site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

يسمح موقع Forex Trader And Short Url لشركات اخرى مسماه خادمات إعلان ( طرف ثالث مثل **[ Google Adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense/)** ) او شبكات الإعلان, لخدمات الإعلانات ضمن موقع مسلسل كوم و اقسامه الاخرى تستعمل هذه الخدمات إعلان ( طرف ثالث ) او شبكات الإعلان تقنية لإرسال مباشرة إلى متصفحك, فـ الإعلانات والروابط التي تظهران على موقع مسلسل كوم يستلمون عنوان الأي بي بشكل آلي وهم ايضاً قد يستعملون تقنيات اخرى ايضاً مثل ( خزن الكوكيز, او جافا سكربت, او اضافات اخرى ) لفهم فعاليات إعلاناتهم ولإضفاء طابع شخصي على الإعلانات التي تناسبك .  

Forex Trader And Short Url does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks  Forex Trader And Short Url to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the  Forex Trader And Short Url Sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. 

موقع  Forex Trader And Short Url شخصياً لا يزود اي معلومات هامة او غير هامة إلى خادمات إعلانات طرف ثالث, او شبكات الإعلان دون موافقتك او ما عادا ما تحتاجه عند عرض اعلاناتها على موقعنا ويمكنك انت في اغلب الاحوال ان تختار قبول او عدم قبول من خيارات متصفحك, فمثلاً اذا احتاج المعلن في مسلسل كوم لعرض إعلانات إلى جمهور مهتم بالبحث عن مواضيع حول كبار السن فشركات الإعلان هذه ستفهم انك مهتم لهذا النوع من المواضيع وسيتم اضافتك لقائمة هذه المواضيع واضهار الإعلانات مشابهه لما تطلب دائماً لكن لن يتم اخذ اي معلومات شخصية اخرى منك .

  إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي مزيد من المعلومات أو لديك أية أسئلة عن سياسة الخصوصية ، لا تتردد في الاتصال بنا عن طريق البريد الالكتروني التالي : [ daa3em@gmail.com](mailto:daa3em@gmail.com)  أو الاتصال بنا من 

_[ هنا](http://www.forex-url.net/contact)_

فريق عمل  [ Forex Trader And Short Url](http://www.forex-url.net/) ... أعيد تحرير هذه الصفحة بتاريخ 28-08-2009 . 

بنود هذه السياسة قابلة للتطوير والتغيير في محتواها في أي وقت نراه ضرورياً
